Apex Predators is a horror film directed by Dustin Ferguson.
The bodies of beach goers begin washing ashore during the
grand opening of a new resort with dire results.
Kirk Williamson, played by Raymond Vinsik Williams.
Rebecca Romaine, played by Mia ScozzaFave.
Dr. Charlene Brinkman, played by Brinke Stevens.
Momma Maria, played by Maria Olsen.
Super Model, played by Alana Evans.
Dr. Juke Westwin, played by Thom Michael Mulligan.
Apex, titled Apex Predator in the UK, is a 2021 American science fiction action film
directed by Edward John Drake and written by John Drake and Corey William Large.
It stars Neal McDonough and Bruce Willis and was released on November 12, 2021.
The tone is dark.